http://www.acc-uk.org/privacy-policy

Members Login
To facilitate provision by Christians of quality counselling and pastoral care. ACC Counsellors now offering on-line and telephone counselling
To facilitate provision by Christians of quality counselling and pastoral care
Toggle navigation
Find a Counsellor
Find a Christian Counsellor/Supervisor/counselling organisation
What is Counselling?
Why use an ACC Counsellor?
ACC European Contacts
How do I complain regarding a counsellor?
How do I complain about staff or ACC?
Frequently Asked Questions
Become a Counsellor
What is Christian Counselling?
So you think you want to become a counsellor?
Blogs
Combatting stress and burnout Premier radio interview with Sue Monckton-Rickett
Privacy policy
This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting our website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
What personal information do we collect?
Information you give us.
We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. For example, you may fill in a form in order to request information from one of the listed suppliers. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving our provision of resources and communicating with you.
Automatic collection of information We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many web sites, we may use “cookies,” as a way of temporarily storing information concerning the page you are viewing. This is not personal information; we cannot collect your name or e-mail address unless you explicitly give them to us when you fill in a form. We also collect information on the type of browser and computer you use purely for statistical purposes.
What are cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser and keep records of the pages you visit. These cookies are automatically discarded when you close your browser.
Do we share your personal information?
We do not share any information we collect about you. We share customer information only with the suppliers listed on the site so that they can respond to requests you make when you complete an enquiry form.
We may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is:
reasonably necessary to comply with the law
to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions
to protect our rights and those of the user
Links
Where there are links on our site to other sites the content of those linked sites is not covered by this privacy policy. These other sites will have separate privacy and data collection practices. We do not have responsibility or liability for these independent policies. Links to other sites are provided by us for information only and in good faith. We are not responsible or liable for any content advertisement, product or other materials on or available from such sites.
Similarly, in passing your enquiry via e-mail to our suppliers we cannot be held responsible or liable for how your information is handled by these suppliers.
What options do I have?
As discussed above, you can always opt not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make an enquiry for goods or services.
Terms and Conditions, notices and revisions
Your use of the acc-uk.org.uk website and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, and application of English law. If you have any concern about privacy at ACC please send a thorough description to office@acc-uk.org and we will try to resolve it. Our service to you evolves over time. This Policy and the Terms and Conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.
ACC is not responsible for any content published on this website by a third party.
You should check our web site frequently to see recent changes.
